哦天啊
Oh,boo ya.
来让姐看看他们葫芦里卖的什么药
Now let's see what all the fuss is about.
真是印第安纳琼斯真人秀
Oh,this is so Raiders.
*法柜奇兵电影*
但愿这个方舟别有那么多烧纳粹脸的神器
Here's hoping this Ark contains less Nazi-face-melting goodness.
哦，Una Mens
Oh,the Una Mens...
啊！
Oh!
不错，他们来了
Indeed.They are coming.
他们还很饿
And they will be hungry.
啊啊啊啊啊
Aaahhh!
放开我，僵尸男!
Let me go, zombie boy!
Whicher,等等
Whicher,hold on...
她是有主的人类
She is claimed.
可她居然有胆子置血圣法律于不顾
Yet dares to defile the blood laws.
她要被送去见Una Mens
She will be delivered by the Una Mens.
你还该去看牙医呢，兄弟
And you need to be delivered to a dentist,buddy.
你的口气比大脚怪的菊花还臭
Your breath smells like the anus of a Yeti.
*大脚怪 类似神农架野人一样的雪山生物*
你这冲进庇护所的人类还真是嘴炮不打草稿
Bold talk from the human who attacked a place of sanctuary.
Whicher,你在犯错误
Whicher,you're making a mistake.
你应该放开她
You should just let her go.
我早说了，我不是人类
I keep telling you I am not human.
这真可爱
That's cute.
看见了吧，她不是你要找的人
As you can see,this one cannot be the one you're looking for.
她是……
She is...
里里外外都是异种，亲
All Fae,baby.
感受下这热量
Feel the heat!
这怎么可能？
How is it possible?
我错了吗？
I am mistaken?
嘿，人人都素会犯错滴
Hey,pobody's nerfect.
我们会把她弄走的，尊敬的大使
We'll get her out of here, your emissary.
下次爷再看见她，就扒了她的皮
The next time I see this one,her skin will line
装饰Una Mens的神圣密室
the Una Mens Holy chambers.
我刚才绝对就要打赢他了
I totally had him.
走吧
Let's go.
多谢了，啥都不干探长
Thanks,Detective Do-Nothings.
干嘛，你刚怎么就没用你的大狼爪在他屁股上来两下
What,you couldn't have whomped his ass with your massive wolf paws?
怎么？错过那场好戏？
What,and miss the show?
干得好，小火花
Nice work,Sparky.
肯子，刚刚多危险啊
That was too close,Kenz.
这临时的能力可不是什么好主意
These temporary powers are not a good idea.
是，但是没办法啊，我是恐怖分子，记得吗？
Yeah, but necessary,because I'm a terrorist,remember?
恐怖分子闻起来像向日葵和霞多丽酒？
You terrorists all smell like sunflowers and Chardonnay?
好吧，我可要把Tinkerbell带回家了
Okay,I'm gonna take Tinkerbell home,all right?
*Tinkerbell 彼得潘里的小精灵，小仙子*
没错
Yep.
你先去吧
After you.
我得交公文
I'll go do the paperwork.
向日葵？
Sunflowers??
真不错
Nice.
没人啊这里，Dyson
No one's here,Dyson.
别闻了
Stop sniffing.
就你，我，和丁字裤，对吧？
Just you,me and the,uh,thongs,huh?
哈
Ha.
那可是一堆丁字裤诶
That's a whole lot of thongs,by the way.
恩，我要说，这可都是生意需要
Well,I will have you know,that these are all business thongs.
我还是别问的好
I don't even wanna know what that means.
我倒是看得出你为什么需要这些东西
I can see why you need all this stuff, though.
为了让这地方显得不那么空吧
Sort of fills the place up a bit.
恩，我又不孤单，如果你指的是这个的话，狼仔
Well,I am not lonely,if that is what you're asking,wolfie.
我不是这意思，真的
I wasn't,actually.
和我在一起你为什么会觉得孤单？
Why would you be lonely with me here?
这可是个，好问题
That is a very...good question...
妈的
Shit...
所有狼都这么浪漫吗？
Are all wolves this romantic?
我只是想到了Hale, 我……
I'm just thinking about Hale,I...
你还真开放
That's very open-minded of you.
他为你疯狂，对吧？
He's crazy about you,right?
我们什么时候开始，这样了
Since when are we...this?
议会的傻x又来了
More Council douche-hats.
不是，闻起来……挺不错的
No, smells a little too,uh...pleasant.
你好
Hello.
请进
Please...
我是来找那个天才私家侦探的
I need to speak with the talented private investigator.
我叫Aife
My name is Aife.
我记得你，女士
I remember you,lady.
你把那个说话蝙蝠侠范儿的Ash炸成渣渣了
You made Ash who talks like Batman,go boom.
这天气还穿麂皮？
Oh, suede,in this weather?
真是漂亮到爆
You beautiful badass.
让她走
Let her go.
我不是来打架的
Look, I'm not here to fight.
我需要人帮忙找我女儿
I need help,finding my daughter.
她叫Bo
Her name is Bo.
Bo
Bo.
听起来像个汉子名，是吧？
Kind of a dude's name,am I right?
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  ╮(╯▽╰)╭
英文字幕：来自互联网
翻译：Neffititi，骷髅头正宫_K        精校：Neffititi，Joy，潜行的五    压制：Neffititi
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途
4x01 - In Memoriam
你是个淫妖？
So you are a Succubus?
那个企图暗杀光明异种长老的淫妖
The Succubus who tried to assassinate the Light Fae elders.
我气昏了头
I was agitated.
现在呢？
And now?
没那么气了
I'm less agitated.
而且我有其他目的
And I have a higher purpose:
为了找我失踪的女儿
to find the daughter that I lost.
哦
Oh...
我们见过
we've met before.
我可不怎么记得
You didn't leave much of an impression.
呵呵，亲，我见过的男人多了去了
Ha.Darling,I've 'met' many men before.
不管他们之后怎么跟他们女朋友说的
And whatever they claim later in front of their lady friends
他们可都印象深刻
they're always impressed.
但我说的是最近
But I was speaking more recently.
在Taft的实验室
At Taft's...lab.
对了，你也在那
That's right,you were there.
你有个30岁的女儿？
So, you have a thirty year old daughter?
没人听说过，没人见过的成年女儿？
A grown daughter no one has ever heard of,or seen?
是的，没有她的记录
It's true,there's no record,
也没有我曾生育的证明
or physical indications that I ever gave birth.
淫妖的身体就是她的武器
Though a Succubus' weapon is her body
不会有什么损伤的
so there would be no wear and tear,so to speak.
你要亲眼看看吗？
Would you like to see for yourself?
检查你有没妊娠纹？算了吧
Scanning for stretch marks? Pass.
我内心里知道我生了个女孩
I know in my heart I gave birth to a baby girl.
我知道我肯定给她起的我妈的名字
I know I would have named her after my own mother.
我知道这就是她
And I know this is her.
一看到照片我就知道了
I knew as soon as I found the photo.
赌5块钱是她猫的照片
Five bucks says it's a picture of her cat.
我没疯
I'm not crazy.
这妹子……好漂亮
This woman is...beautiful.
恩，要是你喜欢外在的话，随便了
Yeah,if you're into,like,faces and bodies.Whatever...
我们不接这单
We're not interested.
不好意思啊
Sorry...
我懂，你们不信
You're skeptical,I get it.
我爸可不是把我当傻瓜养大的
My Daddy didn't raise no fool.
那是个记忆线圈
That's a Recuerdo coil.
是有异种在改造她记忆的铁证
That's hard proof that a Fae has been messing with her memory.
我就想知道为什么
I just want to know why.
我会给钱的，当然
I'll pay,of course.
我会给你们一大笔报酬
I'll pay well.
一个女儿，马上就来
One daughter,coming right up.
自然的，银货两讫，你懂
With,you know,expenses,naturally.
自然的
Naturally.
不好意思
Excuse me.
等等，现在？
Wait,now?
每天都这时候
Same time.Every day.
你都找了一个月了，啥也没找着啊
You've been going for a month and you have found squat.
她救了我的命
She rescued me.
Dyson，她把车开下悬崖的
Dyson,she drove you off a cliff.
我要没变身就死了
And I would have died if I hadn't shifted.
这就是为什么我得找到Tamsin
That's why I need to find Tamsin.
我要知道为什么
Find out why...
好吧，你记着你丢下我跟客户，还有账单
Okay,you owe me for leaving me alone with the client,and the tab.
好消息，她接你的案子
Good news.She's gonna take your case.
你很幸运，Kenzi是最棒的
And you're lucky,cuz Kenzi is the best.
我也得走了，这周可是舰队周
I'd like to get going,as well.It's Fleet Week.
*Fleet Week 海外服役的美军舰队回国靠岸的一周，船员们可以进行娱乐活动*
好吧
Okay.
您还要点什么吗？
Can I get you anything else?
让我来吧
Allow me.
太好了
Great.
我现在手头有点紧
I'm a little short right now.
*Bo曾在S01第一集中在相同位置说过完全一样的台词*
我以后会回来
Maybe I could come back sometime,
补偿你
make it up to you...
太好了
God...yes.
妹子，你需要个管家
Lady,what you need is some kind of manager.
啊啊啊啊
Aaaahhh!!!
新嗜好？
New hobby?
是因为你和Stella的事吗？
Is this because of what happened between you and Stella?
啥？
What??
不是，啥事也没有
No.Nothing happened.
啥也没有是指就是分手了还是说你没把她肚子搞大
Nothing like it's just a break or nothing like you knocked her up.
别碰
Don't touch...!
有些事不大对头
Something's out of step.
有人在乱搞时空的平衡
Someone's been messing with the balance of space and time.
我敢说是新的议会
My money's on the new Council.
他们好像很烦的样子
They seem really easily butt hurt.
呃……
Ugh...
Una Mens就是无所不能的议会
The Una Mens are a near-omniscent council
隶属于异种权威，唯一目的是……
of Fae authority who's sole purpose...
是确保古老法律得以施行，呵呵
is to ensure the old laws are followed.Uh huh.
那种子是个什么？
What's with the seed?
是Una Mens的标志
It's a symbol of the Una Mens.
他们从天而降到我们的小世界是因为
They're descending on our little colony because
前几年一团乱
things have gotten real messy in the past few years.
都是比博热的错
I blame Bieber Fever.
他们，呃，他们不会搞……
They,um,wouldn't do...
记忆丧失什么的，对吧？
memory loss,would they?
不，Una Mens根本就不会动这种不起眼的手脚
No,the Una Mens would never stoop to something so...subtle.
等等，为什么问这个？
Wait...why?
哦，恩，新客户
Oh,uh,new client.
我要知道附近哪个异种能造成失忆
I need a beat on the local Fae that can cause amnesia.
失忆？
Amnesia?
是的
Mm-hmm.
恩……
Uh huh.
Snook医生
Dr. Snook.
他是个Ortenax，鱼怪，吸食记忆
He's an ortenax;fish Fae;feeds off memories.
*Ortenax 一种欧洲传说中的鱼，握着这种鱼的骨头就会丧失记忆*
平时就是个眼科医生
Moonlights as an eye Doc.
鳟鱼眼医，明白了
Trout-tometrist.Got it!
说到医生，有Lauren的消息吗？
Speaking of Doctors, any word on Lauren?
她先是违抗了Ash，又在手术里把Taft骗了
She tricked Taft during surgery,after disobeying the Ash.
她抛弃了光明异种
She abandoned the light Fae.
她救了Dyson的命！
She saved Dyson's life!
很难想出有什么事能让她失控
It's always been difficult to know what makes Dr.Lewis tick.
因为她笨拙，循规蹈矩又害羞
That's because she's awkward,and formal and shy.
她一生的爱已经死了
The love of her life is dead.
Lauren失去了Nadia，还非得为那些杀了她的人工作
Lauren lost Nadia,then had to keep working for the people who killed her.
总之她是我唯一的人类盟友了
Anyway,she's the only other human ally I've got.
尽管我都不太像人了
Even though I'm barely human these days.
我们有人在找她
We have people looking for her.
恩，你都说过好多次了，老爹
Yeah.I've heard that one before,Gramps.
搞怪老爹，Trick
Trickster.Trick.
先生
Sir.
多谢你了
Thank you.For this...
一切小心
Just be careful out there!
恶魔脸有千千万
Evil comes in many faces.
我看到了好多Gucci和Prada
I'm seeing lots of Gucci and Prada...
恩，磨皮手术，肉毒针
Uh huh...dermabrasions, botox.
恩恩
Mm-hmm.
你们好
Hello!
Janet
Janet!
Janet，医生在吗？我们得见他
Janet, is the Doc in? We need to see him.
那种笑容骗我上下床还行
Now,with a smile like that, you could talk me
进门可没门
into your bed,but not through those doors.
在我叫警察前赶紧消失
Now,skedaddle before I call the cops.
真警察
The real cops.
或者
Or...
好，好，好，好吧
Ow,ow,ow,ow,okay!
坐下，坐好
Sit.Stay.
打个滚？
Roll over?
嘛里嘛里哄
Jeepers Peepers...
你不用解雇保姆
You don't have to fire the Nanny.
就没有什么出轨的事
The affair never happened.
你老公在帮Olga做韧带拉伸
Your husband was only helping Olga stretch.
帮助妻子忘记她们丈夫的不忠？
Helping wives forget their husbands cheated on them?
多伟大的人啊
What a noble calling.
Snook医生，我们得问你几个问题
Dr.Snook.We have some questions for you.
你好像在乱搞不该搞的人的记忆
Seems you've been messing with the wrong people's memory.
我这没事了Janet,你能，恩，把账结了吗？
We're done here. Janet,could you,um,get the,uh,bill?
来吧亲，这边走
Come on,darling.Okay...this way.
恩，真好
Yep,you were great.
这边走，好的，看看你……
This way...okay.Oh,look at you
干得不错，兄弟
Nice one,buddy.
对于你们这些鲸察来说，我，恩……
As for you curious carps,I'm,um...
嘿，嘿，Snook，冷静点
Hey,hey!Snook,chill.
就是问几个问题而已
Just want to ask you a few questions.
不不，对不起，Snook只取记忆
No,no,sorry.Snook only does memory extractions.
可不会放回去
He does not restore them.
不过，这可真是漂亮的杰作
Although,that is some beautiful work
你在说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
我想我们忘了
I guess we forgot.
哦……
Oh...
如我所料，变形男有个记忆线圈
as expected,the shifter does have a Recuerdo coil.
但就像Snook说的……不是我干的
But like Snook explained,this is not my work.
好吧，好吧你的意思是别人在
Okay.Okay,so what you're saying is somebody's
提取我们的记忆？
been in here extracting our memories?
恩恩
Mm-hmm.
这好烦
This is very disturbing
是的，你的意思是我能出名
Yeah,you're telling me.I could be famous.
我能成卡戴珊？
I could be a Kardashian?
你大概有点害羞
You could be shy.
人类和异种里谁能造成失忆
Who has the power to cause amnesia,in both humans and Fae?
天赋异禀的……
Someone very talented
比Snook强得多的某人
and someone infinitelymore powerful than Snook.
记忆有自身的轨迹
A memory spell of this magnitude
你要找到并摧毁记忆指南针
you'd need to find and shatter the Recuerdo compass.
诡异， 哪找得到？
Wicked,vault it to me.
淘宝？异极极？
Ebay?Fae-jiji?
指南针在马达加斯加海岸丢失了
The compass was lost off the shore of Madagascar
当Esme Fierce号沉没的时候
when the Esme Fierce ran aground.
哦，不妙
Oo,burn.
但传说，有个人花了一大笔钱
But rumor has it,that someone's paid quite a bit of money
把它打捞起来了
to have it salvaged.
真是棒！谁拿着呢？
Nice save!So who's got it?
收藏家Engelram
Engelram.The Collector.
Una Mens之前的狂热开趴爱好者Engelram？
Last-bash-before-the-Una Mens permanently party
poops-all-over this town Engelram?
恩？
Yes?
呕！
Ugh!
我听说他的异种古董
I hear he keeps his gallery of antique-y Fae swag
都锁得紧紧的
well under lock and key.
干嘛，我关注有钱异种的交易啊
What,I keep tabs on wealthy Fae dealings.
为了我的科学
For my science.
恩哼
Mmm...
但以防万一，我要叫Dyson去给我们
But just in case,I will tell Dyson to score us
弄两张那个何弃疗的傻x的宴会票
two tickets to this loser recluse's shit show.
不喜欢高大上的社交活动？
Not a fan of a nice strawberry social?
和异种？看着他们吃吃喝喝，跳舞谈情
With the Fae?Watching them dance and drink
然后他们还吸食我们？
knowing that they feed on my kind?
还有他们的光明/黑暗系统虚伪得可笑？
That their whole Dark/Light system is completely hypocritical?
不，谢谢
No,thank you.
你有机会穿漂亮裙子
You get to wear a pretty dress.
我得走了，多谢你的乌龙茶
I gotta jet. Thanks for the Oolong.
恩，你忘了点啥吧？
Um...Aren't you forgetting something?
我们是忘了点啥
We are all forgetting something.
我的王野之戒？
My Kingmoor ring?
谢谢，还有什么？
Thank you.Anything else?
我那夏夜妹子的限量版！
My Lass of the Summer's Eve collector's item!
你知道他们只生产了1000个？
You know they only made a thousand of these?
女孩子总需要有口饭吃
Girl's gotta eat.
这是什么？
What's this?
哇哇哇，你还好吗？
Whoa,whoa,whoa...are you okay?
告诉我你们客户的所有情况
Tell me everything you know about your client.
噢，不不不，我没有生气，亲爱的
Oh.No,no,no.I'm not angry,darling.
我是由衷的感兴趣极了
I'm genuinely intrigued.
当我说给我制作最后一件
When I say design me one last costume
“适合新黑暗异种领袖的服装”
"befitting the new Dark Fae leader"
你为什么听成:“把我打扮成性感洗剪吹？”
why do you hear:"Dress me like an asexual hobo?"
我......我......（啊-啊-啊......）
I...I...（A-a-a...）
我是真真的希望你意识到Engelram的派对
I-I-du-du-do hope you realize Engelram's party
是本季最重要的大事
is the event of the season
也是我最后疯狂的机会
and my last chance to get the freak on.
议会来了以后,就要把所有乐子暂停了
Before the Council arrive,to put the moratorium on all fun.
像这样的乐子,比如
Fun like this,for example
Vex
Vex!
你没有权利进入这里，大丹麦狗马默杜克
You got no authority here,Marmaduke.
*Marmaduke:美国卡通狗形象，经常令主人哭笑不得*
权利？我只看见一个恶霸在动武
Authority? All I see is a bully taking out
他正在解决妈妈依恋症
his Mommy issues on the help.
你不能阻止我变身,Vex
Vex You can't stop me from shifting,Vex.
一旦我变成了狼,我会直攻你的喉咙
And once I'm a wolf,I'm going straight for your throat.
好吧，我生来就顽固不灵
Yeah,well,I'm as stubborn as I am well endowed.
而且我挺喜欢墨西哥式决斗的
And I do love a good Mexican Standoff
*指三人持枪对立僵持局面，首先开枪的人占优势 *
噢？
Ol?
顺便说下，照片不错
Nice picture,by the way.
对，我和别人一样惊讶于
Yeah,I was as stunned as anyone to find out she had
她会指定我为黑暗王位的继承者，可以这么说
named me heir to the Dark throne,so to speak.
我当时内牛满面
I shed so many tears.
但我必须坚强
But I had to stay strong.
因为这是马桶逝世姐也想看到的
It's what Miss Died-on-the-toilet would have wanted.
而且你的前任会对你说什么
And what would your predecessor say to you
如果你给你的光明派异种敌人
giving your Light Fae enemies...
进入今晚收集者舞会的门票?
tickets to the Collector's ball tonight?
恩，你什么时候开始喜欢上舞会了？
Hmmm...Since when have you liked balls?
我们需要找回我们遗失的东西
We need to get backsomething we've lost.
我特马凭什么要帮你们？
And why the hell would I help you do that?
因为如果你不帮的话
Because if you don't
我可能必须要告诉Una mens
I may have to tell the  Una Mens that you...
你夸大了年轻的Evony死亡的细节
exaggerated the details of young Evony's demise.
什么？
What?!
我能闻到她就在后面，Vex
I can smell her back there,Vex.
在小黑屋里
in her little cell
她死了
She died
噢，她的确腐坏了，对
Oh,she's rotten,all right,
但是她并没有腐烂
but she's not rotting.
没胆子做完全套吗？
Not man enough to finish the job?
你何弃疗
You're mental.
这对Evony来说是一个耻辱，你知道么
It's a shame about Evony, you know?
虽然她既邪恶又疯狂但她是强敌
She was evil and insane,but she was a worthy foe.
而且比你做领导好上十倍
And ten times the leader you'll ever be.
好消息是
The good news is...
你嘴里吐出三张去Engelram那个小聚会的邀请函
you cough up 3 invitations to Engelram's little shin dig.
我就不会暴露你
And I won't rat you out.
你觉得怎么样
What do you say?
Cynthia?你能不能给我们的警探Dyson
Cynthia? Could you provide Detective Dyson
准备豪华派对入场券？
with our complimentary party tickets?
没错！我的入场券!
Yes! My tickets!
看来我不需要它们了
Looks like I won't be needing them.
感激不尽，Vex
Thanks a bunch,Vex.
当然了，我不保证如果我拿回我的记忆
Of course,I can't guarantee that once I get my memory back
我会让你继续保留这份轻松的工作
I'll let you keep this cushy little job.
以及你的性命
Or your life.
别对我笑了，你这沾沾自喜的碧池
Stop smiling at me,you smug bitch.
啊哈！
Aaahhh!!!
这里以前举办过烈酒之夜
This used to be a spirit night.
我以前是Ash，现在是屌丝
I used to be the Ash and now I'm a disgrace.
别在公众场合看着我哭
Don't see me crying...in public.
很多美女晃动她们，呃，身体上宏伟的部分
Lot of ladies shaking their, uh... baby grands.
不是说我介意
Not that I mind...
对，这个
Yeah,well...
每年，一个女孩会被选中得以会见难以捉摸的收藏者
every year,one girl gets chosen to meet the elusive collector.
难以捉摸的，意味着肮脏的富有
Elusive,as in,filthy rich.
这不是说他拥有多少金钱,收藏品，或者异种们珍贵的记忆
It's not the money,or his collection of priceless Fae memorabilia.
Engelram是两头蛇
Engelram's amphisbaena.
*两头蛇:西方传说中可以同时向两个方向移动的怪物*
*吃掉其肉可以吸引异性，心灵纯洁的人满月时将其杀死可以获得无穷的力量*
可以让愿望实现的异种？
A wish granter?
是的
Yep.
所以某个幸运的女人可以实现她心里最深的欲望
So some lucky lady gets her deepest desires granted.
真真是极好的
That's nice.
我希望我的女人能来这
I wish my lady would get here.
脚丫沟？
Toe cleavage?
真正的乳沟？马达哈利假发？
Real cleavage?Mata Hari wig?
*与Bob发型类似的女士假发造型*
侬好！
Holla!
我是Kenzi
It's Kenzi.
呃，我知道我们过去没有总是...很合得来
Uh...I know we weren't always...copacetic.
但我现在可以在撞色搭配方面用上你的书呆子理论
But I could use your nerdy hypothesis on some color blocking right now.
还有，呃，我只是希望，你现在安全
And,um...I just hope...you're safe.
所以
So...
Lauren,如果你听到这段留言，回我，回我电话
you know,if you get this, call me, call me back...Lauren.
好，挂了
Okay,bye.
你最好到这里来告诉我怎么搭配饰品的
You better be here to advise on accessories.
我的新玩具，你想靠近看仔细点吗？
My new toy.You want a closer look?
噢,我刚说什么了？
Oh,what am I saying?
你这样的女孩，总想让人靠近看仔细点
Girls like you always want a closer look.
你干什么去了那么久?
What took you so long?
我给你打电话了,一个小时前就打了
I called you,like,an hour ago.
这玩意儿不会抽它自己
This stuff doesn't whip itself.
仔细想想，我也不会
Come to think of it,neither do I.
把它给我
Give it to me.
哇，火花精华
Wooo...Spark extract
直接从精灵生殖器里提取出来的
mined straight from the genitals of a sprite.
得了，别王婆卖瓜了
Ya,don't oversell it.
你得让专家来干这事
You better let a professional handle this.
恩……
Mmmm...
就这样？
That's it?
你已经用完你的最后两次预约了
You're already on the books for your last two visits.
我知道
Noted.
当然如果现金是问题的话
Of course if cash flow is a problem
总有其他方法付款
there are always other ways to pay.
你没有让我变成异种
You didn't make me Fae.
你骗了我
You tricked me.
现在我只是个火辣的人类
Now,I'm just a hot human
在闪闪的精灵服里脑补着
sheep in twinkly fairy clothing.
那你脱掉我精心打造出来的伪装
So shed my brilliantly concocted disguise
看到时候议会
and see what happenswhen when the Council
来敲你家门的时候会发生什么
comes knocking on your door.
Massimo, 拜托
Massimo,please.
我会给你钱的
I'll get your money.
好的，或者下次
Good.Or next time
我会以有牙齿的造型出场
I'll show up with something with teeth.
也许我该去质问那个人？
Maybe I should interrogate that one?
你觉得呢?
What do you say?
你确实喜好独特
You certainly got a type.
Kenzi
Kenzi?
噢，额滴神啊
Oh,my God...
Hi...你觉得如何？
Hi.What do you think?
我觉得你迟到了
I think you're late.
而且Engelram已经看上某人了
And Engelram already has his eye on a favorite.
姐还是能拿到指南针的，引起他的注意
I can still get the compass. Get his attention.
你引起我的注意了
You've got my attention.
听着，我只是说你不用狼
Look,I'm just saying you don't bring a wolf
来保护小羊羔
to guard the sheep.
什么意思？
What does that mean?
你看见那两人了吗？
You see those two?
她们经常出现在运动杂志的封面
They've been on the cover of Sports Illustrated.
我喜欢运动
I like sports.
我只是说虽然你有各种天赋
I'm just saying that despite your many talents
但是这次可能稍微超出你的擅长范围了
maybe this is a little outside of your area of expertise.
我是说，我们现在需要一个接吻大牛
I mean,we need a killer kiss here.
我会让你知道的
I will have you know
我以前色诱过不少笨蛋土豪
that I have seduced many a rich-dork before.
我觉得
I think.
行了，你到底想不想把我们的记忆找回来？
Okay, do you want to get our memories back or not?
然后忘记这梦幻一刻？
And forget this magic moment?
你想看看姐的本事？
You wanna see my skill set?
好吧，我希望你做过暖身了
Fine.I hope you stretched.
嗨，你能给我买杯酒么？
Hi!Can you buy me a free drink?
似曾相识
Deja Vu
不，我是Cilo
No,I'm Clio.
似曾相识还有一箱的螃蟹
Deja Vu came down with a case of the crabs.
迷死人
Charming.
噢，额滴神啊
Oh,my God...
我认识你
I know you.
哇，你是警察
Wow...you're a cop.
不管这是什么?我不感兴趣
Whatever this is?I'm not interested.
我是个Nymph
I am a nymph.
*Nymph 希腊、罗马神话中居于山林水泽的仙女，与蚕蛹、幼虫同音*
现在我真的不感兴趣了
Now I'm really not interested.
艾玛
Ouch.
只是有些不好的记忆
Just bad memories, you know?
龙舌兰浸泡过，赤裸裸的
Tequila-soaked, nakedness.
你知道，我们不是所有人都那么坏
You know, we're not all bad.
我们只是孵化成那样了
We're just kind of spawned that way.
一，二，三，四
One,two,three,four...
别数了,Hale
Stop counting, Hale.
把我抱紧点，我不是你的Nona
And hold me closer, I'm not your Nona.
*Nona: 命运三女神之一，主管怀孕*
别乱蠕动了
Stop squirming.
我去，搞得好像你想把我衣服撕掉一样
Dammit,act like you wanna tear my clothes off!
噢，天哪
Oh,golly.
这比你试着跟人拉家常更怪
That's more awkward than your attempt at small talk.
我同意
I agree.
抱歉
Excuse me.
我挺好的，拍档
I got it,partner.
你还真没有
You really don't.
那棕发女人是谁？
Who's the brunette?
你能不能闭嘴让我好好领舞一次
Would you just shut up and let me lead for once?
真的吗?
Seriously?
也许我们以前这样做过
Maybe we have done this before.
那我特定会记得
That,I would remember
最后的玫瑰
The final rose.
真是原汁原味
How original.
看来有人要去私密的会议室了
Looks like someone's going private chambers.
海盗臀，当然了
Pirate booty,sure.
独角兽填充娃娃，干嘛不
Stuffed unicorn...Why not.
你好?
Hello?
好大的门
Great door!
声音真响
Really loud.
而且我喜欢你所有的笼子,非常的高端大气上档次
And I love all your crates. Very Pottery Barn.
*Pottery Barn:美国家具公司，专门设计舒适有格调的品质家具*
这种情形是突然求婚的节奏吗？
Is this situation going in decent Proposal?
因为姐需要先看到珠宝呈上，伙计
'Cause I'm gonna need to see the jewels up front, buddy.
欢迎光临，漂亮的女孩
Welcome...pretty girl.
Engelram先生？
Mr.Engelram?
为您服务
At your sssservice.
请不要因为我而停下!
Please,don't stop yourselves on my account!
今朝有酒今朝醉!
Diddle your souls while Rome burns.
明日愁来明日愁!
Make merry while ye may!
Una Mens已上路
For The Una Mens are on their way!
我也开始我旅途
And I'll be on mine,too!
直到你呈上我
As soon as you cough up what I
值得尊敬的黑暗派领袖所想要的
the venerable leader of the Dark,want.
而我想要的，是狼人
And what I want is the Wolf.
嗷呜
Ooowwww!
我能让你付点代价就出去
I can get you out of here for a price.
我觉得我应该留下，撕开他的喉咙
I think I'd rather stay; rip out his throat.
既是morrigan又是mesmer？真假？
The Morrigan,and a mesmer? Seriously?
你知道怎么绕绳下降么？
Do you know how to rappel?
为什么，你那小不点裙子里有绳子？
Why,you got some rope in that itty bitty dress?
我一定要自己做完所有事吗？
Do I have to do everything...myself?
噢，Snook
Oh,Snook.
噢，你现在只有你自己了，狼人
Oh,you're on your own,Wolf.
你究竟是什么
What are you?
我是谦卑的异种记忆收集人
I am a humble gatherer of Fae memorabilia
热爱你舞蹈的大粉丝
a big fan of your dancing
而且我是两头蛇
And I am Amphisbaena.
悠着点儿, 斯莱特林
Slow your roll,Slytherin.
*Slytherin 斯莱特林 哈利波特中霍格沃茨四大学院之一 以蛇为院徽*
我只想看看里面
I merely want to look inside.
我会让你没说出口的愿望实现
So I may grant your unspoken wish.
不用，我要说出口
No need,I'll speak it.
我想要里卡多·蒙塔尔班
I want the Ricardo Montalban...
*里卡多·蒙塔尔班:好莱坞70年代明星，经常饰演拉丁型情人*
瑞奇·马丁
Ricky Martin...
*瑞奇·马丁:勾勾勾，啊泪啊泪啊泪*
啊 那个指南针
Uh, the, the Compass thing-y.
就这样
That's it?
嗯，我还想要带走你的独角兽
Well...I'll take your unicorn too
如果你想要换小点的房子
if you're looking to downsize.
当可以满足你无限制的愿望时
Just when it comes to unlimited wishes
你变得浮浅了
you kind of landed on sssshallow.
那什么，你是话事人
Well,you're one to talk.
就跟你那奇怪的能力都不要钱似的
Like those toddler-esque pores happen au natural.
现在，现在
Now,now.
我只用每两个月蜕皮一次
I simply shed my skin every two months.
那不公平
That is so unfair.
你可以试试
You could try...
在你午夜吃喝着芝士爆米花和伏特加
removing your makeup before you pass out
昏昏欲睡前卸掉你的妆
atop your midnight helping of cheese popcorn and vodka.
喵
Me-ow.
回到手上的任务了？
Back to the task at hand?
对，抱歉
Right.Sorry.
我只不过以为弱小的人类会许愿
I merely thought the little human would wish
让她回来
for her return.
不
No.
还有，什么
Also,what?
可怜啊
Pity.
你不知道你究竟失去了什么
You don't know what you're misssssing.
我知道在你把我整个吞下前
I know I'd like to get out of here
我想离开这里
before you swallow me whole,so...
谢谢侬
thank you.
你称我为人类
You called me human.
我早该意识到了
I should have realized it ssssooner.
你的探戈有些瑕疵
There was something so vulnerable about your tango
噢，眼镜蛇指挥官
Oh,Cobra Commander.
*眼镜蛇指挥官:美国漫画G.I.Joe里自负的反派角色*
我实现你的愿望
I granted your wish
现在，我要把你整个囫囵吞下
now I "am" going to swallow you whole.
这交易很公平不是吗
Isn't that a fair trade?
服装很漂亮，Vex
Nice costume,Vex.
你不是去年最重要的混蛋么
Weren't you the impotent dick last year?
看看谁是真正的贱人的时间到了
Well,now it's time to see who really is the bitch.
以及谁刚死了
And who's just dead.
你跋山涉水跑这来
Did you come all the way down here just
就为了给我显摆你漂亮的新鞋子？
to show me your pretty new shoes?
不是，这是关于记忆的
Hardly.This is about remembering.
或者确保没人保有（记忆）
Or, making sure that no one else does.
你的记忆也消失了
Your memory's gone,too.
我早百八十年就猜到了
I worked it out ages ago.
这样才科学,说真的
It's the only thing that makes sense,really.
现在感觉越来越不科学了
This is making less and less sense.
你觉得我是做Morrigan的料吗？
Do you really think I was meant to be the Morrigan?
我从来没有真正的获得权利，我说，不像现在这样
I've never really had power before.I mean,not like this.
而且会不会
And what if...
所有人记起来的事情
the thing everyone remembers leads them
会让他们挑战我辛苦得到的王位
to challenge my hard-fought reign?
我做了很坏的事来重获我的能力
I did terrible things to get my mesmer back.
即使对我来说
Even for me.
Vex，听~海哭的声音
Cry me a river,Vex.
我还是会做我变得无助的噩梦
I still have nightmares about being helpless.
没法影响人,没法吸食
Unable to influence.Unable to feed.
但是
But,this...hm...
现在是最好的局面了
this is about as good as it gets for me.
如果我让Kenzi和别人记起来没有我有多好
And I'm damned if I'm gonna let Kenzi let everyone else
我就玩儿完了
recall how good it was to be without me!
这怎么行得通，Vex
How's this going to work,Vex?
一旦我变身你就不能催眠我了
You can't mesmer me once I shift.
对，但是我能够催眠你的妹子
Yeah,well...it's a good thing I can mesmer your mate!
Vex，别让她牵涉进来!
Vex!Leave her out of this!
斗转星移
Evan-nescence!!
啊！
Ugh!
你什么时候也开始这么戏剧性了？
Since when do you do the dramatic?
你想要狗血？
You want drama?
我要结果了你
I'm gonna end you.
小笼子
Small crate
大笼子，蛇男要来了
big crate,snake man coming
来吧，Kenzi
Come on,Kenzi
来吧，你这无依无靠又无能的发光棒
come on,you no friends,no talent,Glow Stick... !
好吧
Okay...
付我钱
"Pay me."
不，不，不
No,no,no.
偏偏是在这时候成为人类！
Of all times to get my human back on!
你和我们是一伙的！
You fought by our side!
有罪
Guilty!
你背叛了我们关于Evony的条约!
You betrayed our agreement about Evony!
猛一点
Harder!!!
你爱kenzi，你怎么能这样对她
You love Kenzi! How could you do this to her?!
我们都爱kenzi
We all love Kenzi.
你的大哥正上她呢！
Hell, your Alpha Male's 'doing' her right now...
前任Ash真的要杀掉现任Morrigan吗？
Is the former Ash really gonna kill the current Morrigan?
我觉得Una Mens不会喜欢这样
I don't think the Una Mens would like that.
只有一个办法知道他们喜不喜欢
There's only one way to find out.
啊！
Ah!
大狼爪子
Massive Wolf Paws...
忘了告诉你了，我喜欢你的发型
Forgot to tell you:love the hair.
噢,天啊
Oh,my...
Aife?
好久不见了
It's been a long time...
你好,爹爹
Hi,Daddy.
指南针
The Compass!
它碎了
It cracked...
那么，究竟成功了没？
Well, did that do it?
不,你还有鸡翼咸圈（记忆线圈）
No,you still got canola oil.
等等...也许我们得把指针对准真正的北方
Wait...maybe we have to align the needle to the true North.
收到
Roger that.
Kenzi
干毛？
What?
你总是在我身边
You've always been there for me.
你也是
And you for moi.
我愿意为你献出生命
I would give my life for you.
我绝对不会遗弃你
I'd never desert you.
也许Vex是对的
Maybe Vex is right.
也许现在这样最好
Maybe this is as good as it gets.
也许
Maybe...
也许我们能更好
Maybe we can make it better.
我有，八十条丁字裤
I...have,like, eighty thongs.
那棒极了
Well,that's great.
我是说，我很孤独
I mean...I am...lonely.
而且这是用来，这所有的，都不对劲
and this for...all of it,it isn't right.
这并没有太久
It hasn't been for awhile.
而且我……而且我的心很痛
And my...And my heart hurts.
Dyson,我不知道为什么
Dyson,and I don't know why.
另外，当你陷入爱河，你懂的
Besides,when you're in love,you know.
对吧
Right?
对
Yeah.
不管发生什么，你和我都会一起战斗，对吗
Whatever happens,though,you and me,we're in it together,right?
对，朋友如手足，女人如衣服
Yes.Friends till the end. Bros before hoes.
Dal的酒友小伙伴
Pals at the Dal...
对，就那些有的没的
Yeah,all that.
对
Yeah.
把它给我
Gimme that.
啊
Ugh...
Bo...
啊
Ugh!
不
No.
爹爹
Hi...Daddy.
Aife
Aife.
Aife，拜托
Aife,please...
那是我唯一剩下的东西了
It's all that I have left.
那唯一让我活下来的是我的仇恨
It's all that's kept me alive! Is my hate!
我知道我们总有一天会再见面
Knowing one day we would have our reunion.
然后以你抛洒你那被诅咒的热血而终
And it would end in you spilling your cursed blood.
我会为我们找到她的
I'll find her for us.
这是为了她
This is for "her"!
Hale！Hale，你还好吗?
Hale!Hale,are you okay?
噢，他没事
Oh,he's fine.
高效率华丽丽的美人魚音
Very effective.Splendid siren-ing.
Kenzi，你知道，我很欣慰你没有被蛇咬
You know,I'm glad you didn't get bitten by the snake,Kenz.
而且我要告诉你
And I gotta tell you,I love what you're doing
我爱死你这几天的睫毛妆了
with your mascara these days.
姐也爱死了
I do,too.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry
不，打住
No,stop
打住，我们要找到她
stop,we're going to find her.
她失踪多久了?
How long has she even been missing?
我们该从哪开始找？
Where do we even start?
不管是谁抹杀了我们深爱的人的记忆
By finding whomever could have erased
我们就从他开始找
the memory of the one we love most.
噢,你会后悔的
Oh,you'll regret it.
这涉及到古老狂野的魔法
There lies some old, wild magiks.
不,不,不......不,Dyson.你现在不能走
No,no,no...No,Dyson,you can't go now!
最后看见Bo活着的人是Tamsin
The last person to see Bo alive was Tamsin.
那你还等什么?!出发，出发
Well,then what are you waiting for?!Go,go!!!
啊
Ugh...
你还好吧
Are you okay?
Kenz......我们需要谈谈
Kenz...we need to talk.
等她回来再说,我都不能......呼吸了
Not until she's back.I can't even... breathe.
我要走了,好我要走了
I gotta go.Okay,I gotta go...
Bo?
Bo...
哦......我记得......
Oh...I remember...